Finding aid for Abdeen Jabara papers, 1956-1994 0234 Aa 2
Bentley Historical Library
- Political and Cultural Activities
  - Israeli Human Rights Abuses (Publications and Literature), 1968-1975; 6 folders (Box 11)
  - Israeli Prison Conditions, circa 1983-1985; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Jonathan Jay Pollard Espionage Case, 1984-1986 (Box 11)
  - Khalil Toame Defense Committee (Box 11)
  - Land Financing Course Notes, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Lebanon, 1975-1976; 1983-1984
    - Amin Gemayal's Visit to Detroit, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence (Box 11)
    - FOIA Requests, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Notes (Box 11)
    - Press Clippings (Box 11)
    - Resumes (Box 11)
    - Statements and Resolutions (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 11)
    - General Miscellaneous (Box 11)
    - Middle East Literature, 1968-1972 (Box 11)
    - Palestine Digest (scattered issues), 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Press Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box 11)
    - Unpublished Mellison Article (Box 11)
    - Zionism & Racism and a poem written by Jabara, 1967; undated (Box 11)
  - National Association of Arab-Americans (NAAA)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Membership Guidelines Binder, circa 1973 (Box 12)
    - Press Clippings, 1973 (Box 12)
  - National Lawyers Guild (NLG) Middle East Delegation
    - Book Review from Brooklyn Journal of International Law for NLG Report, 1980 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1979; 1981; 9 folders (Box 12)
    - Correspondence (Arabic), circa 1976-1977 (Box 12)
    - Guild Notes and other Press, 1975-1978 (Box 12)
    - In the Struggle Newsletter, 1975; 3 issues (Box 12)
    - Jerusalem Post (scattered issues), 1975 (Box 12)
    - Majority Report of NLG Concerning Treatment of Palestinians in Israeli Occupied Territories, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Minority Report of NLG on Treatment of Palestinians in Israeli Occupied Territories, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous Reports and Papers, 3 folders (Box 12)
    - Press Clippings, 1976-1979 (Box 12)
    - Resolutions, circa 1977-1978 (Box 12)
    - Statements, Interviews, etc., circa 1976-1977 (Box 12)
  - Nazareth Democratic Front (Box 12)
  - Operation Boulder
    - Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1972-1976 (Box 13)
    - Court Cases Involving Investigation and Harassment, 1971 (Box 13)
    - The FBI and Domestic Intelligence by John T. Elliff, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Press Clippings, 1972-1979; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Organizing Committee for Clemency for Sirhan (Box 13)
  - Palestine Human Rights Campaign
    - Bulletin, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
    - Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1980 (Box 13)
  - P.L.O Detroit Visit, 1976 (Box 13)
  - Socialist Workers Party Case (vs. Attorney General), 1983 (Box 13)
  - South Lebanon Prisoners
    - ACCOUNT records, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Collection (newsletter), 1982-1983 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
    - International Center for Information on Palestinian and Lebanese Prisoners, Deportees and Missing Persons, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
    - Lawyers Statements, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - News Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
    - Palestinian Cultural Heritage Association (P.C.H.A.) records, 1982-1985 (Box 13)
    - Red Cross Communications, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Testimonials, 1982 (Box 13)
  - Stephen Franklin Articles, undated (Box 13)
  - UAW Arab Workers Caucus
    - Articles and Papers, undated (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1973-1974 (Box 13)
    - Press Clippings, 1973 (Box 13)
  - U.S. Aid to Israel
    - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 13)
    - Papers and Press Clippings, circa 1982-1985 (Box 13)